Contact

6026254321 (Mobile) swsiamon@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ samuelsiamon (LinkedIn) ssiamon05.github.io/portfolio/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

JavaScript React.js Git

Samuel Siamon

Front End Web Developer Seattle

Summary

Recent graduate from the University of Washington. I graduated with a BA in mathematics and a minor in informatics. I am hoping to hone and strengthen my web and software development skills as I continue on my search for a job right for me. I have experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js, Firebase, and Git.

Experience

Mathnasium - The Math Learning Center Teacher January 2020 - Present (1 year 9 months) Ballard, Washington, United States

Sylvan Learning Teacher March 2019 - January 2020 (11 months)

Firehouse Subs
Team Member
March 2018 - September 2018 (7 months)
Phoenix, Arizona Area

Education

University of Washington

Bachelor's degree, Mathematics · (September 2018 - August 2021)